Hello!
Come on!
Today I'm not at home, but in Stockach-Wasis at Benno von Stein's new showroom.
I think it's great that you're here and that you're visiting us in the new showroom.
I'm really happy because it's nice to get out there and see what I've built up here.
The show hasn't been around for very long.
Basically for four weeks.
For four weeks.
And that's an idea, just to show the complete creative power of me as a designer and to invite people who are interested in my things to come and see me here, to try the new parts and to get them excited.
And that also excites me and that's why I'm trying something now.
Well, they're sitting.
This dress is brand new.
And that was also available in a slightly longer version.
That was this one, so for significantly longer.
This was our first collection with this kind of clothing and many women have come to us.
They would like to have it a little shorter to show their beautiful long legs.
I think it's shorter than that too.
And that's new now with a newly constructed plissi collar.
What I find very nice is that it is lying on top and then the optics open up so that you can combine a nice necklace like you are wearing now wonderfully.
My favorites are just beautiful stools that work well in a material that has micropores.
You don't sweat that much in there.
What is that material?
an artificial leather. Such a small self-development, because we have always been told that artificial leather,
plastic sheets, you sweat a lot in there and through the micropores it is reduced.
And the hole leather is more transparent anyway, through the whole punch. It is also an artificial leather and
I always like to combine it because I have an optics through such a seam, an
empire line or a part to emphasize again. The man has a clue, there is a clue behind it.
I learned it and for good reason I also use my designs with the know-how.
I like that about you, that everything is with push buttons, that you can turn it on and off super quickly,
everything is adjustable in size, partly, so variable and I just like that. Is actually also the concept of
With zippers and push buttons, the hair stays in very little.
Every velcro is the natural enemy of one.
I've now looked around what I want to wear and I discovered this.
I heard it's a prototype.
This is my newest area in which I am researching a neck corset suitable for a thallium
miter and a small overhair.
That's what you can just pull on and off like that.
We can see how it looks here.
I'm excited!
I'm not a fan of neck corsets because I have a relatively short neck, but I'm just trying it now.
And I don't have a mirror yet, so it always depends on how tight you want to wear it.
I'm not going to do it all the way to the top yet. I'll leave it like this for now.
I imagined it to be worse. No, it's okay. I'll probably never be a big fan of the
Halsgesetz, but I have to say it fits very well, especially with the rest. And the color,
it's cool. It's something different from black, it's not too wild anyway. I think the darker
silver, in my personal preference, is a bit better because it's just a bit more black.
But the combination is cool. It's not quite such a harsh contrast as between the
light silver and black, for example. And I still get air. Yes, that's no problem. And it's
not uncomfortable either. So before all the questions come again.
What do you think is better with or without a neck corset? Write it in the comments. I'm
curious. I definitely feel a little better without a neck corset, but we're going back to
black again because tie-in corset and body in black is, I think, also quite cool again.
The optional leash.
The optional strap.
It sparkles.
And of course it's pure taste.
Exactly.
I think that's a little cooler than the silver one before, just because I like black and it's so rocky somehow.
I think the detail is super cool with this asymmetrical zipper here.
And this jumpsuit, whatever.
I think it's mega. It's also super comfortable.
Okay, what is that material? You wear a body made of artificial leather, but this
new corset I designed is a real leather. Cashed in artificial leather, because the
rods are glued between the two materials and then sewn so that this function
is also there, but I can only do that with a really nice, well-colored rind leather.
Okay.
Wouldn't it be a great idea to stretch real leather?
Yes, it's also available on the market. There are different qualities of stretch leather and I'll just show you the best one.
Is that what's there?
Exactly.
A really good lamb napa stretch leather is simply unachievable in terms of wear comfort.
I would also not like to make these qualities, because I think the greatness of the material in connection with the size and the optimal cut and fit is the best.
I also respect this material and my quality, to be a master tailor for 30 years, is to bring it to the point, to get the optimal out of it.
And this body feeling that is set in by that, that's actually what it's about.
I take measures, I do the advice and I hear exactly what needs are there.
And if the possibility to come here is to our newly opened showroom, it is optimal.
I have all the materials there, I have all the models there.
It is the complete selection of all the designs that I have made.
I can't present something like that at a trade fair.
All right, then go.
Yes.
This is stretch leather.
This is stretch leather now.
you can also stretch it. Really stretch. And?
That's so cool. What I'm wearing is actually also stretch leather.
It's equipped from the inside with a carrier material, which stretch leather
, but it doesn't jump back. And these cached inner fabrics
are just so that they always pull the leather back into the shape and you
smear much less in the material. I've been here in the men's department
and there's also a bit of paint and chic pants, as I find for men.
quite a lot. Oh look, also leather jackets, masks, and, well, hairpins. I think there are both open-middle and
without glitter. Oh yes, here is also one without strass. Already a lot of choice.
Oh, that has a net in the back.
Well, let's get started. And what I discovered, you may know from the other video, the
chic cat suit.
and went all in. It's a leggings and a coat and we put on a corset.
A completely different look, but I think it's also very cool. Actually, the coat is a
few numbers too big for me, but you don't notice that at all because of the corset. We say goodbye to the outfit
now. Thank you very much for the invitation. Nice that you were there. Yes, it was so nice here in the showroom.
You can touch everything, look at everything, try it, get advice, also with the measuring machine.
Really super cool. I can only recommend it to everyone. If you have the opportunity, come by.
Come by. If you have the opportunity, look around. Come around here at Benno von Stein.
And we're going to have another coffee now. Wonderful, with pleasure. And say goodbye. Bye.